export const hazardQuestions = [
    {
        question: "It is a kind of mudflow composed of a thick, soft, and wet texture of pyroclastic material.",
        optionA: "Volcanic Gas",
        optionB: "Avalanche",
        optionC: "Lahar",
        optionD: "Mud Slide",
        correctOption: "optionC"
    },

    {
        question: "Which of the following is NOT included in the said hazards?",
        optionA: "Ashfalls",
        optionB: "Typhoon",
        optionC: "Lava Flows",
        optionD: "Ballestic Projectiles",
        correctOption: "optionB"
    },

    {
        question: "Upon reading our information, on what landforms of the Earth that these hazards occur?",
        optionA: "Buildings",
        optionB: "Mountain",
        optionC: "Hills",
        optionD: "Volcano",
        correctOption: "optionD"
    },

    {
        question: "Gases produced by active volcanoes.",
        optionA: "Oxygen",
        optionB: "Volcanic Gas",
        optionC: "Ash Falls",
        optionD: "Volcanic Tsunami",
        correctOption: "optionB"
    },

    {
        question: "It is a linear volcanic vent through which lava erupts.",
        optionA: "Debris Avalanche",
        optionB: "Pyroclastic Density",
        optionC: "Lateral Blast",
        optionD: "Fissuring",
        correctOption: "optionD"
    },

    {
        question: "It is a steam of molten rock that pour from an eruption event.",
        optionA: "Lahar",
        optionB: "Fissuring",
        optionC: "Volcanic Gas",
        optionD: "Lava Flows",
        correctOption: "optionD"
    },

    {
        question: "A kind of tsunami that was produced by a volcanic event.",
        optionA: "Mountain Tsunami",
        optionB: "Tropical Tsunami",
        optionC: "City Tsunami",
        optionD: "Volcanic Tsunami",
        correctOption: "optionD"
    },

    {
        question: "It is a volcanic eruption that is directed laterally or from the side of a volcano rather than upwards from the summit.",
        optionA: "Pyroclastic Density Currents",
        optionB: "Lateral Blast",
        optionC: "Debris Avalanche",
        optionD: "Fissuring",
        correctOption: "optionB"
    },

    {
        question: "Considered as the most dangerous hazards that local areas may experience during a volcanic event",
        optionA: "Pyroclastic Density Currents",
        optionB: "Fissuring",
        optionC: "Lateral Blast",
        optionD: "Lava Flows",
        correctOption: "optionA"
    },

    {
        question: "Caused by a collapsing unstable slope that normally happens on a sharp volcano.",
        optionA: "Debris Avalanche",
        optionB: "Lahar",
        optionC: "Ash Falls",
        optionD: "Volcanic Tsunami",
        correctOption: "optionA"
    }
];

export const safetyQuestions = [
  {
      question: "Which of the following is NOT considered usefull in a Safety Health Kit?",
      optionA: "Basketball",
      optionB: "Medicine",
      optionC: "Band Aid",
      optionD: "Betadine",
      correctOption: "optionA"
  },

  {
      question: "Which of the following is the safest place to go when a volcanic hazard occured?",
      optionA: "Volcano",
      optionB: "Collapsing Building",
      optionC: "River",
      optionD: "Evacuation Center",
      correctOption: "optionD"
  },

  {
      question: "3. Which of the following is NOT included in the group?",
      optionA: "Ethanol",
      optionB: "Face Mask",
      optionC: "Telescope",
      optionD: "Band Aid",
      correctOption: "optionC"
  },

  {
      question: "You should always close the ______ damper.",
      optionA: "Water",
      optionB: "Air Condition",
      optionC: "Fireplace",
      optionD: "Window",
      correctOption: "optionC"
  },

  {
      question: "The volcano alert level ranges from 0 to ___.",
      optionA: "3",
      optionB: "5",
      optionC: "4",
      optionD: "7",
      correctOption: "optionB"
  },

  {
      question: "There are over 300 volcanoes in the Philippines, how many are considered active?",
      optionA: "28",
      optionB: "20",
      optionC: "32",
      optionD: "24",
      correctOption: "optionD"
  },

  {
      question: "There are areas we should avoid near a volcano when an eruption is imminent, what are these areas?",
      optionA: "River Valley Downstream",
      optionB: "Lake",
      optionC: "River Flows",
      optionD: "Meadow",
      correctOption: "optionA"
  },

  {
      question: "It is a volcanic eruption that is directed laterally or from the side of a volcano rather than upwards from the summit.",
      optionA: "Pyroclastic Density Currents",
      optionB: "Lateral Blast",
      optionC: "Debris Avalanche",
      optionD: "Fissuring",
      correctOption: "optionB"
  },

  {
      question: "Where should you go when there is a volcanic ashes in your current location?",
      optionA: "Building",
      optionB: "Clinic",
      optionC: "Temporary Shelter",
      optionD: "Supplies Store",
      correctOption: "optionC"
  },

  {
      question: "An eruption could be triggered by:",
      optionA: "Magma Intrusion",
      optionB: "Air Craft",
      optionC: "Bouyancy",
      optionD: "Lava Collapse",
      correctOption: "optionA"
  },

];